SINEM CELENK

MBA | Marketing Professional



Vancouver, B.C Canada

HELLO -

Enthusiastic about new trends, and consumer behaviors. Skilled in marketing, project communication, strategic management, thinking, and leadership. Manages every step of the marketing project from initiation to closure. Enjoys conducting market research and finding new market opportunities. Expert in external and internal communication management. Possesses broad creative experience with multiple brands such as L'Oréal Paris, Enterprise, Kotex, Kleenex, Huggies.

CONTACT -



celenksinem@gmail.com



sinemcelenk



sinem.space

SKILLS & ABILITIES



CRM



Market Research & Analysis



Strategy & Planning



Marketing



B2C Marketing

Marketing





Event

Management

Relations



Creative Thinking

Leadership

References available upon request.

EXPERIENCE

MARKETING PROJECT MANAGER

Sparktank Franchise Marketing | June 2021- present

- Managing digital local and franchise recruitment campaigns.
- Working together with web developers, and designers.
- · Coordinating the work distribution.
- · Managing client relationships.

MARKETING SPECIALIST

Teskilat ICOM Advertising Agency | May 2018 - October 2018

- · Managed digital and conventional advertising campaigns for a global car rental company.
- · Organized workflow to meet team goals and deadlines.
- Managed the creative team, Managed team and client meetings, campaign, and event budgets, marketing campaigns, and budgets.

MARKETING SPECIALIST

A.N.D.B.R.A.N.D Advertising Agency | Nov 2017 - May 2018

- Managed advertising campaigns for Halkbank, Aytemiz Gas, Real Group Construction, Ekin Safe City Technologies.
- Prepared weekly working plans for the creative team and clients.
- "Halkbank European Tour" advertising campaign has chosen toprated, remembered, and spoken ads of 2017 by Ipsos Ad*Watch.
- Managed the "Halkbank 80th anniversary" advertising campaign which was the biggest campaign of the brand and was displayed in 81 provinces in Turkey during 2018.

PUBLIC RELATIONS SPECIALIST

Essance Istanbul Communication Consultancy | Feb 2015 -Nov 2016

- Developed corporate communications and PR Campaigns for global FMCG companies.
- · Assisted in developing competitive marketing strategies.
- Organized PR, Corporate Social Responsibility campaigns, Celebrity & Influencer management, and communication plans. Completed all the projects within an approved budget, timescale, and expected quality.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY CANADA WEST

2020-2021 - Vancouver

Master of Business Administration (MBA) 3.61/4

LCC COLLEGE

2019-2020 - Vancouver

Professional Communication and Marketing Diploma Program with CO-OP

ISTANBUL UNIVERSITY

2010-2014 - Istanbul

Bachelor's degree in Public Relations and Advertising 3.15/4